Finding Aid for the Livingston Gearhart Collection of Scores, 1930-1996
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Manuscript score additions, circa 1940-2004, V; Folder 508-663
  - Additional arrangements, circa 1940-2004, V.B; Folder 520-663
    - Arrangements for instrumental and vocal ensembles, circa 1960-1990, V.B.3; Folder 559-612
      - Purcell, Henry, 1659-1695 Of old when heroes thought it base. And in each tract of glory Air adagio de Mr. H. Purcel, from an early 18th century collection 1976, 1 score (1 page); Holograph (Pencil) For two unspecified treble instruments. Marked Bass in caption. (Box 31, Folder 600)
      - Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943 Morceaux de fantaisie, op. 3. Sérénade; arranged Serenade undated, 1 score (17 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For orchestra. Lacking title. (Box 31, Folder 601)
      - Ravel, Maurice, 1875-1937 Sonatina, piano. Mouvt. de menuet; arranged Multi purpose minuet undated, 1 score (7 pages) and 5 parts; Holograph (Pencil) For violin, oboe, or flute with string orchestra. (Box 31, Folder 602)
      - Satie, Erik, 1866-1925 Gymnopedies. No. 3; arranged Gymnopedie #3 undated, 1 score (8 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For orchestra. (Box 31, Folder 603)
      - Seitz, Friedrich, 1848-1918 Schüler-Konzert, no. 2. Allegro non troppo; arranged Concerto undated, 1 score (14 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For orchestra. (Box 31, Folder 604)
      - Simandl, Franz Neueste Methode des Kontrabass-Spiels. Bd. 1. Übungen in der V. Lage. No. 8; arranged Etude undated, 1 score (4 pages) and 4 parts; Holograph (Photocopy) For solo double bass (or cello) and string orchestra. Includes photocopy of printed Exercise no. 8 from Simandl's New method for the double bass. Parts titled Fat-man etude. (Box 31, Folder 605)
      - Simandl, Franz Neueste Methode des Kontrabass-Spiels. Bd. 1. Übungen in der V. Lage. No. 8; arranged Etude undated, 1 score (2 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For solo double bass and string orchestra. Includes photocopy of printed Exercise no. 8 from Simandl's New method for the double bass. On folder: New version. Accompanied by typescript explanatory note. (Box 31, Folder 606)
      - Squire, W. H. (William Henry), 1871-1963 Tarantella, cello, piano, op. 23; arranged Tarantella undated, 1 score (13 pages) and 5 parts; Holograph (Pencil) For solo cello and string orchestra. Accompanied by typescript explanatory notes (2 leaves). (Box 31, Folder 607)
      - Star-spangled banner (Song); arranged Star spangled banner undated, 2 scores and 2 sets of parts; Combination of manuscript and print For orchestra. Consists of photocopy of holograph score (4 pages) and parts (27) with editing marks in preparation for publication and copy of printed score (8 pages) and parts (28) with corrections noted prior to publication by Ludwig Music (2005). Accompanied by correspondence concerning the editing process from Fritz Gearhart to Pamela Gearhart and Pamela Gearhart's manuscript draft of program and biographical notes to be used in the published version. (Box 31, Folder 608)
      - Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741 Estro armonico. N. 6. Selections; arranged Concerto undated, 1 score (15 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For solo violin and string orchestra. (Box 32, Folder 609)
      - Warren, George William, 1828-1902 National hymn tune; arranged God of our fathers 1977, 1 score (19 pages) and 16 parts; Combination of manuscript and print For chorus (SATB) with 2 pianos and band. Delaware Water Gap, PA: Shawnee Press, 1977 Parts are photocopies of manuscripts; the score is the published version by Shawnee Press Words by Daniel Crane Roberts. (Box 32, Folder 610)
      - Yankee doodle (song); arranged Jankj dydl: Overture to Act XXIV [by] Moussourgsky undated, 1 score (7 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For orchestra. Yankee doodle arranged in the style of Modeste Mussorgsky. (Box 32, Folder 611)
      - Compositions by Livingston Gearhart: Blue packet undated, 1 spiral bound volume (127 pages); Holograph (Photocopy) For varied instrumentations, chiefly string trio. Chiefly arrangements by Gearhart. (Box 32, Folder 612)
        Fugue in G minor / J.S. Bach – To a wild orchid: Take II – Misty / Erroll Garner – KimPam / L. Gearhart – Prelude #4 / Chopin – Pastorale / Stravinsky – Pavane of the sleeping beauty / M. Ravel – Iste confessor – Greensleeves – Bouree I and II / J.S. Bach – We wish you a merry Christmas – God rest ye … -- First noel – Good King W. – We 3 kings – Silent night – Bachianas Buffalonis -- Auld lang syne – Antiques refinished (the series) [Minuet in G major] – Variations on a British air / by Livingston Gearhart, edited by Fritz Gearhart – Ala fanfare, for horn, trumpet, and string orchestra – Kyrie for string orchestra / by Livingston Gearhart – Short suite for string orchestra / by Livingston Gearhart.
    - Pedagogical works, 1975-2004, V.B.4; Folder 613-663
      Arrangements made for use in pedagogical compilations and settings. After Livingston Gearhart's death, Pamela and Fritz Gearhart continued to edit many of the works for possible publications. Their correspondence and markings are included.
      Arranged alphabetically by title of the pedagogical compilation.
      - Gearhart, Livingston Bass quartet undated, 7 folders; Holograph (Pencil) For double bass quartet. Original works and arrangements by Livingston Gearhart. Received in a folder marked Bass quartet and placed in order as listed on folder. (Box 32, Folder 613-619)
        Fandango -- Malaguena (formerly Fandango) -- Elegie: experimental compression -- Theorem I -- Oh come all ye faithful -- Equali / Beethoven -- Elegie (Thanatopsis).
      - Gearhart, Livingston Hommage a Suzuki 1975-1987, 7 folders; Holograph (Pencil) For string quartet, quintet, and sextet. Variations on Twinkle, twinkle, little star as performed in the Suzuki method. (Box 32, Folder 620-626)
        I. Prelude or Introduzione: for string quartet (1 score and parts) -- II-III. 2 pieces from Hommage a Suzuki: for string quartet: Minuet; Air (score and parts) -- IV. How I wonder what you are: variations on a hidden theme: Scherzo: for string quartet (1 score and parts) -- V. Nocturne: for 3 violins, viola, and cello (1 score and parts) -- VI. Marche inevitable: for 3 violins, viola, and cello (parts) -- VII. Lullaby of Matsumoto: for 3 violins, viola, cello, and bass (1 score and parts) -- IX [sic]. Epilogue: for string quartet (1 score, parts with Lullaby parts).
      - Gearhart, Livingston Rhythm sessions: a duet book for treble clef instruments undated, 1 score (49 pages); Holograph (Photocopy) For 2 unspecified treble clef instruments. Title on cover: Compositions by Livingston Gearhart: Yellow packet (Box 33, Folder 627)
        A plague of rests -- Any kind of note can get one beat --Hide n' surprise -- Not how you heard it (3 versions) -- Agony one -- Another shot at the dot -- Melody -- Same but different -- Melody II -- Veni Emmanuel -- Veni meni mini mo -- Music of Athens (Georgia, that is) -- Subtraction game -- Take away one -- Then two -- Etcetera -- Double or nothing -- Old time Gershwin favorite, The man I love -- The grand total -- Take away two -- Add one -- Take away two -- Gotcha? -- Ostinato mit Veranderungen -- Le coup de grace -- If this doesn't kill you we'll keep working on it --Inward counting I -- Inward counting II in 3/4 -- Inward counting I -- Inward counting II in 3/8 -- Boris and Natasha -- Air / modified Purcell -- Take away one -- Eleven suspensions -- Variations on a tune from Petrouchka -- Interpolations -- Untitled work aus Bach -- Ever increasing agony I and II -- 3 views of a syncopated scale -- Rhythmic imitation I and II -- Theme from Finlandia (3 versions) / Sibelius -- All tied up I-III -- Silent nightmare I and II -- Minimal melody -- Hopak: Patterns on a scale of F -- You got rhythm? -- Blues pattern -- Two against three -- Exhaustion I and II -- The entertainer / Joplin -- Bethena: ragtime waltz / Joplin -- Ragtime rhythms / Debussy -- From Exercise no. 5 (School of ragtime, Joplin, 1908) -- Ragtime workout -- Mixed-up meter. -- Fragment of Le sacre du printemps / Stravinsky.
      - Gearhart, Livingston Rhythm sessions: for string orchestra 1995, 6 parts (violins 1-3, viola, cello, and bass); Print For string orchestra. Copyrighted by Fritz Gearhart 1995. (Box 33, Folder 628)
        Giggle rhythmics -- Canon challenge in five -- Rhythm antics -- Valse incredeeble -- Noodle zoop -- Survival of the fittest -- Mississippi hotdog agony -- Pfui -- Suite: Land of liberty.
      - Gearhart, Livingston Rhythm sessions: for strings 2004, 1 score (45 pages); Print For string orchestra. Grafton, Ohio: Ludwig Music, 2004 Accompanied by correspondence from Fritz Gearhart to Pamela Gearhart and explanatory notes. Proof copy marked with corrections. (Box 33, Folder 629)
        Rhythmic morphing -- Canon challenge in five -- Rhythmic antics -- Valse incredeeble -- Noodle zoop -- Survival of the fittest -- Mississippi hot dog agony -- Pfui -- Suite land of liberty -- Sospirando -- Madrigal madness -- Cross rhythms: a canon at four bars -- Malaguena -- Scale stuff -- Rhythm glossary.
      - Gearhart, Livingston Rhythm sessions: for strings 2004, 1 score (45 pages) and 6 parts; Print For string orchestra. Grafton, Ohio: Ludwig Music, 2004 Lacking title. Marked with durations and suggested corrections. (Box 33, Folder 630)
        Rhythmic morphing -- Canon challenge in five -- Rhythmic antics -- Valse incredeeble -- Noodle zoop -- Survival of the fittest -- Mississippi hot dog agony -- Pfui -- Suite land of liberty -- Sospirando -- Madrigal madness -- Cross rhythms: a round at four bars -- Malagueña -- Scale stuff -- Rhythm glossary.
      - Gearhart, Fritz Scale stuff: for string orchestra: a comprehensive and versatile daily warm-up collection undated, 1 score (118 pages); Print For string orchestra. Originally based upon content created by Livingston Gearhart. Accompanied by explanatory notes and replacement pages. Marked with suggested corrections. (Box 33, Folder 631)
      - Gearhart, Livingston String mix II undated, 13 folders; Combination of manuscript and print For string orchestra. Consists of materials related to 2nd volume of String mix, including a proof copy of score and parts and individual folders for each of the 11 works proposed for the collection. Works folders include pencil manuscript and computer-notated scores accompanied by explanatory and editing notes by Fritz Gearhart. Materials copyrighted by Fritz Gearhart 1995-1997. Marked with proposed corrections and changes to be made for a final version. (Box 33, Folder 632-644)
        Correspondence -- String mix II spiral bound score and 6 parts -- Scherzino / P.I. Tschaikovsky -- Hatikvah -- Stringerooni -- En'tracte / Schubert -- Slavic tune -- Wounded Knee rock -- Classical muse -- Chorale -- Reverie -- Multi purpose prelude / J.S. Bach -- Mumbo jumbo: Brazilian magic chant [Note: not included in spiral bound score].
      - Gearhart, Livingston Treble clef sessions between 1990 and 1996, 1 score (26 leaves); Holograph (Photocopy) For unspecified treble clef instruments. Contains complete ms. for Treble clef sessions published by Shawnee Press in 2000. It is a reproduction of the manuscript in Folder 423. Marked with corrections and changes in preparation for the final version. (Box 34, Folder 645)
        2.0. Utter simplicity -- 3.0. Beethoven themes I and II -- 3.1. As fast as you can -- 3.3. Suspensions I -- 3.4. Suspensions II -- Variations on a theme from Petrouchka -- The significance of [quarter rest] -- 4.0LR. Inward counting (Two duos) -- 4.1 La campanella / Paganini -- 4.2. Bulgarian melody -- 4.0LR. Inward counting -- 4.3. Mixed metre -- 4.4. Vulgarian music -- 4.5. Andante doloroso -- 4.6. Canon in two speeds -- 4.7 Jazz (Sort of) -- 4.8. Count two (Think four) -- 5.0. Like, Ping pong: Three canons. Volley for serve; 5.1. Backhand; 5.2. Trick shot -- 5.3LR. Interiorization -- V4. Scherzo theme / Beethoven -- Three different ways of writing the same music -- Interiorization -- V5. Any kind of note can get one beat -- V6. Step-by-step progression -- 5.5. We gather -- 5.6. Valse triste -- 5.7. Broadway hit of 1910 / Romberg -- 5.8. Melody / Schubert -- 5.9. Waltz / Brahms -- 6.0. Il botcho / Arditi -- 6.1. From Artist's life -- 6.11 O Logie O'Buchan / Scotch -- 6.12 The unconstant lover (...Is worse than any thief) / Appalachia -- 6.2. Syncopation explication in two movements -- 6.21 Bethena: Ragtime waltz / Joplin -- 6.3. Familiar? -- 6.4. More syncopation in 3 steps -- 6.41. Jazz-related figures -- 7.0. Not a waltz / Grieg -- 7.1. An teicead so heisipt: Flight into Egypt / Irish -- 7.2. Air / Purcell -- 7.3. Unfinished business / Schubert -- 7.4. Kastchei's infernal dance (Theme) / Stravinsky -- 7.5. Rosetta stone I -- 7.6. Rosetta stone II -- Careful!: in three movements -- 8.1. Lament canon at one bar -- 8.2. A displaced rhythm -- 8.3. Sinfonia Brevis -- 8.31. Something hidden -- 9.0. Pavane theme / Ravel -- 9.1. In the garden / Russian -- 9.2. Slightly distorted (Achtung!): [two versions] -- 9.3. Bottom of the Ninth / Beethoven -- 9.4. Double play at (the) third / J.P. Sweelinck -- 9.5. Not the way they sing it -- 10.0 [Published as Challenge I (How many steps can you skip?)] -- 10.1. Two-note tango -- 10.2. Okay, 3 notes -- 10.3. [Published as Challenge II] -- 10.4. Two-note tango -- 10.5. Okay, three notes -- 11.0. Important comparison -- 11.1. Comin' through the rye / Scotch -- 11.2. Comin' through the rye -- 11.3. Erie canal excavated / U.S. -- 11.4. Suez canal -- 11.5. [Untitled] -- 11.6. [Untitled] -- 11.7. Finnegan's wake (He awoke at his wake) -- 11.8. Finnegan's wake -- 12.0 Hopak / Mussorgsky -- 12.1. Putative Amerindian tuned: used by Dvorak -- 12.2. Concerto theme / Handel -- 12.3. Etude / Leopold Mozart -- 12.4. Hornpipe / Brit. -- 12.5. Rough stuff I -- 12.6. Rough stuff II -- 12.7. Chaik II -- 12.8. [Untitled] -- 13.0. Fanfare figure / Verdi -- 13.1. If you have it--reinforce it: [from Tchaikovsky's Fifth symphony] -- 13.2. How come the double dot? (It saves energy) -- 13.3. [Untitled] -- 13.5. Symphony fragment / Wm. Herschel -- 14.0. Sudden action -- 14.1. The interpolator -- 14.2. Calm after the storm / Musorgskii -- 14.3. [Untitled] -- 14.4. [Untitled] / Haydn -- 14.5. The world's longest wait / Chaikovsky -- 15.0. Fussy composers clutter the page. A framework; Embellished; How Haydn wrote it; 15.1. He wanted to stress the idea of separation, as Dvorak did in; 15.2 or, as Chaikovsky did, in; 15.3 But, watch out for this one / Prokofiev; 15.4. [Untitled] -- 16.0. Easing into Ragtime -- 16.1. Exercise no. 5 (from School of ragtime, Joplin, 1908) -- 16.2. The entertainer / Joplin -- 16.3. Golliwog theme / Debussy -- 16.4. The occasional triplet -- 16.6. What's the difference? -- 16.7. Tune from a march / Meyerbeer -- 16.5. Polka rhythm -- 16.8. 6/8: a pair of threes -- 17.0. A most minimal melody (With increasingly vexatious accompaniment patterns) / Offenbach -- 17.1. Tema Espagnole / Lalo -- 17.2. Llwyn on / Welsh -- 17.3. Think six -- 17.4. Think two -- 17.5. Collisions / J.S. Bach -- 17.6. Challenge -- 17.7. Skelsss (Scales with a Russian Accent) -- 17.8. The basic model -- 17.9. Spanish / Rimski-Korsakoff -- 18.0. [Untitled] / Rimski-K. -- 19.1. [Untitled] / R. Strauss -- 18.2. [Untitled] / Half-Bach -- 18.3. Mixed metre -- 19.4. [Untitled] -- 18.5. [Untitled] -- 18.6. [Untitled] -- 19.0. Slow is hard. Wintertime / Schumann; 19.1. Also (Niemals) Sprach Zarathustra / F. Nietzsche; 19.2. Late Brahms; 19.3. Late Bach; 19.4. Polonaise / Chopin; 19.5. Polonaise / J.S. B[ach] -- 20.0. Music of Athens (Georgia, that is) -- 20.1. Motet (Music of the church) / Giovanni Matteo Asola -- 20.3. Veni Emmanuel -- 20.4. Brobdingnagian jig.
      - Gearhart, Livingston Youth makes music 1976, 18 folders; Combination of manuscript and print For string duos, trios, and quartets. Received in a folder marked YMM for Youth Makes Music, the music camp run by Pamela and Livingston Gearhart in Huntsville, Alabama, 1972-1981. The music was written and arranged to serve the pedagogical purposes of the camp instruction for string players. Portion of folder marked with contents inserted in first folder. (Box 34, Folder 646-663)
        For 2 cellos. Agony XXI: Canon at 2 bars; Canon for two at one quarter note; Experimental duos; Fugue on a B-A-D E-G-G; Preludium for two viols / Couperin -- For 3 cellos. 6 variations on Paganini's theme; Bolero; Jericho (Canon for 3 at one bar); Lullaby / Brahms; Marche funebre / Chopin; Passacaglia; Rhapsodie in glue (Glissando study) -- For 3 double basses. Allegro energico; Sort of a waltz (2 versions); Untitled bass trio [1]; Untitled bass trio [2] -- For 4 cellos. BVM (Tempo di Jericho) -- For string quartet. Quartet.
- Published score additions, 1948-1964, VI; Folder 664-676
  Alphabetically arranged by title.
  These scores were received after the processing of the original collection was completed. All of them are arrangements by Livingston Gearhart published by Shawnee Press.nd Erie County Library, Norma Jean Lamb, and the estate of
  - Gearhart, Livingston Gospel train: based on a Negro spiritual: S.A.T.B. with 2-hand or 4-hand piano accompaniment 1959, 1 score (8 pages); Print For chorus and piano accompaniment. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 664)
  - Dolph, Jack, 1895-1962 I'll wait for my love; arranged I'll wait for my love: for mixed voices with optional accompaniment 1963, 1 score (8 pages); Print For voices (SATB) and piano accompaniment. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 665)
  - Gearhart, Livingston Jingle-bell travelogue: s.a. with piano accompaniment 1962, 1 score (8 pages); Print For soprano and alto voices with piano accompaniment. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 666)
  - Gearhart, Livingston Parade of the clichés: full band 1961, 1 score 32 pages) and 53 parts; Print For full band. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Concert Works Unlimited, a division of Shawnee Press, 1961 Publisher number: K 0102. (Box 34, Folder 667)
  - Gearhart, Livingston Parade of the clichés: symphonic band 1961, 1 score 32 pages) and 75 parts; Print For symphonic band. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Concert Works Unlimited, a division of Shawnee Press, 1961 Publisher number: K 0103. (Box 34, Folder 668)
  - Marks, Johnny, 1909-1985 Rudolph, the red-nosed reindeer: for mixed voices with piano accompaniment 1954, 1 score (12 pages); Print For voices (SATB) and piano accompaniment. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press, 1954 Arranger stated as A. Hawley Barry, a pseudonym for Livingston Gearhart. (Box 34, Folder 669)
  - Gearhart, Livingston Sigh no more, ladies: S.S.A.A. with piano accompaniment 1962, 1 score (8 pages); Print For voices (SSAA) and piano accompaniment). Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press, 1962 Composer Orlando Coole is a pseudonym for Livingston Gearhart. Words adapted from William Shakespeare, Much ado about nothing. (Box 34, Folder 670)
  - Monaco, James V., 1885-1945 Sing your way home: camp song: for S.A.T.B. with piano accompaniment 1964, 1 score (7 pages); Print For voices (SATB) and piano accompaniment. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press, 1964 Adapted by Livingston Gearhart. (Box 34, Folder 671)
  - Travis, Merle Sixteen tons; arranged Sixteen tons: S.A.T.B. and piano 1956, 1 score (8 pages); Print For voices (SATB) and piano accompaniment. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 672)
  - Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943 Suites, pianos (2), no. 1, op. 5. Slezy Tears: choral accompaniment to the two-piano work 1948, 1 score (8 pages); Print For voices (SATB) and two pianos. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press, 1948 Score contains piano reduction of the two-piano parts for rehearsal use. (Box 34, Folder 673)
  - Gearhart, Livingston Thanksgiving song: traditional melody: S.A.T.B. accompanied 1958, 1 score 8 pages); Print For voices (SATB) and piano accompaniment. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press, 1958 Words by Wilha Hutson. (Box 34, Folder 674)
  - Gearhart, Livingston Thanksgiving song: traditional melody: S.S.A. accompanied 1958, 1 score (8 pages); Print For voices (SSA) and piano accompaniment. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press, (Box 34, Folder 675)
  - Fauré, Gabriel, 1845-1924 Requiem, op. 48, D minor. Libera me; arranged. English What is man? (Libera me) from Messe de requiem by Gabriel Faure. 1962, 1 score (10 pages); Print For voices (TTBB), baritone solo, and piano accompaniment. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press, 1962 English text by Thulia Snow, transcribed by Livingston Gearhart. (Box 34, Folder 676)
Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog.
Contributors
Gearhart, Pamela; Gearhart, Fritz
Subjects
Music--Manuscripts
Genres
Scores
Associated Material
Additional Guides
Scores in Series I-III in the collection are cataloged in WorldCat and are available in the online catalog for the University at Buffalo Libraries by performing a "Title begins with" search under "Livingston Gearhart Collection of Scores".
Related Resources
Related Resources in the Music Library
Livingston Gearhart Papers, 1933-1997
Mus. Arc. 23.1
Collection contains prose writings, vitae, correspondence, teaching materials, programs, and clippings.
Livingston Gearhart Collection of Photographs,1896-1941
Mus. Arc. 23.3
Collection of 192 images, including photographs of Nadia Boulanger and her summer class of 1938, Gearhart and his first wife, Virginia Morley (Waring) at Mills College in California, with composer Darius Milhaud and his family, and the Budapest String Quartet. The collection also includes four photographs of composer Johannes Brahms in 1896. Also available as a digital collection in
University Libraries Digital Collections
.
Livingston Gearhart Recordings, 1949-2001
Mus. Arc. 23.4
Collection of 23 recordings, including compositions and arrangements by Livingston Gearhart, his memorial service, and the recordings of duo-pianists, Morley and Gearhart.
Related Resources at Other Institutions
Fred Waring's America Music Library
Pennsylvania State University's collection of Fred Waring's music, including some of Livingston Gearhart's arrangements.
Boulanger, Nadia. Scores by American Composers: A Guide.
Ms. Coll. 125
This collection in the Eda Kuhn Loeb Music Library at Harvard University contains five manuscript scores for Livingston Gearhart original compositions.
Piece for Aaron Copland for flute, clarinet, English horn, bassoon, violin, and viola
Prière for "voix d'enfant" and string quartet
Danse russe. Hommage à Igor Stravinsky for 4 trumpets
O Emmanuel for chorus and piano
Rorate coeli for chorus and piano